<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?asciidoc-toc?>
<?asciidoc-numbered?>
<article xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook" xmlns:xl="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" version="5.0" xml:lang="en">
<info>
<title>Freecell Solver Copyright and Licensing Information</title>
<date>2018-09-05</date>
</info>
<section xml:id="licensing">
<title>Freecell Solver Copyright and Licensing Information</title>
<simpara>Relax, this is not GPL software, but rather it is distributed under the
MIT/Expat License ( <link xl:href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MIT_License">http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MIT_License</link> ).</simpara>
<simpara>What this means is that the code and binaries here can be linked against
anything, converted to any different license, freely used and distributed, and
anything else without any restrictions whatsoever. No Strings Attached!™</simpara>
<simpara>&#8201;&#8212;&#8201;Shlomi Fish</simpara>
<simpara>Here is the license text (or "legalese") for most of the code:</simpara>
<screen>Copyright (c) 2000 Shlomi Fish

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person
obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation
files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without
restriction, including without limitation the rights to use,
copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the
Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following
conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT
HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY,
WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING
FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR
OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</screen>
<simpara><literal>kaz_tree.c</literal> and <literal>kaz_tree.h</literal> are distributed under the following 3-clause
BSD license:</simpara>
<screen>Copyright 2009
Kaz Kylheku &lt;kkylheku@gmail.com&gt;
Vancouver, Canada
All rights reserved.

BSD License:

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:

  1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
     notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
  2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
     notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
     the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
     distribution.
  3. The name of the author may not be used to endorse or promote
     products derived from this software without specific prior
     written permission.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED ``AS IS'' AND WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.</screen>
</section>
</article>